- [Narrator] At Meta, we use
information to provide you
with a more personal, secure,
and meaningful experience.
But where does that information come from?
The information we collect
comes from a variety of sources.
One is your activity
on Meta product app services and hardware.
Things like liking an Instagram post,
playing a game on your Meta Quest 2,
buying something through
Marketplace or sharing fundraisers
on Facebook all generate information.
And sometimes businesses
also share information
with us like your activity
on their websites.
They may also share
experiences you have offline,
like signing up for rewards
card with your email address.
This makes it easier for
them to share promotions,
product information,
and other ads with you
through our apps consistent
with the choices you make.
We know that people want to understand
and control what we do
with this information.
That's why we offer a number
of ways to help you personalize
and manage things the way you want.
For example, maybe you've
been shopping around
for a new mattress and
finally found the one.
Now that your hunt is over,
maybe you don't want to see ads
from certain mattress brands anymore.
If so, you can go to Ad Preferences
and hide ads from those
specific advertisers
or manage your ad settings more generally.
Or remember that rewards card?
By signing up, you may start seeing deals
for their products popping up.
Using Off-Facebook Activity,
you can view a summary of the
information Facebook receives
about your activity on
other apps and websites
and choose to disconnect
it from your account.
When it comes to your
information, we're here for you.
And helping you understand
how your information
is collected, used, and
shared is our responsibility.
So whether you're messaging,
posting, shopping, liking,
or sharing, we're committed
to helping you have
the best experience possible
across all of our apps and products.